[Lullaby]
Meera, are you playing with toys?
Look at what Dad brought us--
Camera!
You know,
we have to record videos and show Dad,
how much food Meera's eaten
and how strong she's become.
Oh Meera, you've become so big.
Look there. Look at the
camera, say Hi Dad.
Say it aloud, Hi
Look who's here.
- Hi Mummy, Hi
- Hi Mummy
Record...
Meera's birthday cake is here.
It looks tasty.
- Come on, let's cut the cake.
- Let's go.
1...2...3
[Happy birthday]
[Snapping]
I want my doll.
My Doll, My Doll
My Doll, My Doll, My...
[Screams]
[Doll Music Playing]
Here. Take this money
and go take a break.
Don't worry, here's some more,
go take a break, quickly.
I've bribed the guard.
Is she answering?
What's the plan? Are we going in?
Or is she coming out?
We can't be seen here. We'll be in
big trouble if someone sees us.
Are you mad? Prithvi let's leave.
It'll be a problem
if someone sees us here.
She's here.
- Why aren't you answering your phone?
- Shh....I'll hit you.
How do I get down?
I don't know, just come down.
Ladder, ladder!
Ladder? Go get the ladder.
Perfect
Turn the bike around.
Guys, hurry up.
Okay, stop hitting me.
Let's leave now.
Get off
Here, hold this.
Wait, don't leave me.
[Phone Ringing]
Hello, I'm coming.
This rain just doesn't stop.
Get used to it.
I can't believe we
have to work in this rain.
They don't care about us
Forget it.
[Phone Ringing]
[Siren Wailing]
Prithvi, he's a Survey Officer.
I'll handle it.
You think you're Superman?
Batman?
Or Spiderman?
We told Customs this
place was a mess.
Our work was done.
Why did you want to be a
superhero?
You can't save everyone.
They were going to raid
the place tomorrow.
Tomorrow would've been too late.
The container was supposed
to leave tonight.
Why didn't you call me?
I could've come with you.
Why?
Are you a superhero?
Keep joking around, if something
goes wrong, don't tell me.
Seat belt?
If something goes wrong,
don't tell me.
Hello Papa!
Yes Megha.
What happened to your hand?
I got hurt beating up bad boys.
Oh really!
Isn't it way past your bed time?
If Mom finds out,
we'll be in big trouble.
Congratulations Prithvi!
Morning Sir.
How's your hand?
I'm physically fit sir.
And mentally?
Fit. Fully fit.
You've already
seen his medical reports.
Take a look at this.
We're being praised in the headlines.
Get some sense into him. We
are all answerable to our superiors.
Come!
'Sea Bird' - A dead Ship,
while being towed from
Colombo to Gujarat,
snapped its tow rope due to bad weather
and ran ashore Mumbai's Juhu Beach.
10 stories high and 200 meters long,
this ship did not have
a single person on board.
This is definitely a conspiracy.
Respected Minister, My question to
the Government:
How did this ship
end up here?
As you can see, this massive ship
has landed up on the coast of Mumbai,
and no one knows
how it reached here.
The people
want to know how this happened.
Please move.
[Indistinct Chatter]
This really had to happen right
before my retirement?
How do we get rid of the ship?
What's the plan?
Sir, the ship is stuck
deep in the sand.
It's impossible to move it
until the next high tide.
But how did the ship get here?
- They are still investigating but..
- Sir
I think this is
definitely a conspiracy.
What?
What do you think Riaz?
He's mentally fit sir.
Absolutely fit.
My guarantee.
Is he?
Are you crazy?
[Sirens Wailing]
- Come, let's go!
- I'm coming.
Careful!
Look...
Where are you?
Ghost...
[Phone Vibrates]
JYOTI...
Salvage operations
began early this morning.
The DG Shipping office
is spearheading the operation
with the help of
the Navy and Coast Guard...
It's high tide for the next two days.
We need to get rid of this ship...
- before Agnihotri retires.
- Riaz!
I'm going to go check inside.
Okay!
The Boss is after our lives.
[Indistinct Chatter]
[Doll Music Playing]
What happened?
Why are you so quiet?
No, nothing.
Did you get in touch with Patel?
Yeah, on the phone.
He wasn't making sense.
He was saying the sooner the ship
is scrapped, the better it will be.
Why?
Exactly,
I asked him the same thing.
He didn't say anything at first.
I threatened him a
little so he told me:
"Don't go inside the
ship...it's haunted."
- Haunted?
- Hmm
Why, did something happen?
No, I found out that
this is Patel's old trick.
He spreads a rumor that
the ship is haunted,
then buys it for cheap and
sells it for a huge profit.
Does anyone else know?
No way!
If anyone finds out about this
haunted crap, then that'll be it.
There is no dearth of
superstition in our country.
Just eat.
Nothing's going to happen.
Dad?
What are you doing?
Why are you
looking under the bed?
You won't find any diesel
or sludge here.
Who's calling now?
Hello Sunder!
Hello, I can't hear you.
The network here is terrible.
Where is the diesel leaking?
B Deck?
What? Top Deck.
Give the phone to Mangesh.
Yeah Mangesh, listen.
There's diesel leaking
on the top deck, right?
Is it only diesel?
Or is there sludge also?
There's too much diesel?
Do something. Fill 2 cans for me.
Diesel has become too expensive.
I'm coming there...
Coming, give me 2 minutes.
Yeah, okay bye!
God bless this phone service!
Why are you collecting garbage?
It's just to kill time.
Kill time?
Why don't you play
Scrabble instead?
[Phone Vibrates]
Hello! Yeah, Mangesh.
Yeah, it's me. Tell me.
Where did the diesel come from?
What?
You guys can't do anything properly.
No, until I don't sit on your head,
you won't get any work done.
Riaz...
Riaz.
Is anyone there?
Who's there?
Riaz?
Sunder?
How did this happen?
I fell down the stairs.
Fell down the stairs?
Sometimes it's your hand, today your
leg, tomorrow it will be your head.
- Are you a toddler?
- Riaz, you talk too much.
He just doesn't get it
Riaz, see this.
Prithvi, Prithvi.
[Phone Ringing]
Get some rest, we'll see tomorrow.
Anyway, it's our last chance
tomorrow, we'll figure it out.
Sir...
No sir...it'll get done,
we'll get rid of the ship.
I guarantee it.
The tapes were badly damaged.
I recovered whatever I could.
Thank you!
Hi!
Let's go in.
This is the office.
[Phone Ringing]
Hi! Nilofer
Yeah?
Yeah.
Right now?
No, I'm... Ok.
Is Riaz there?
Alright, no problem.
I'll come.
Come.
Sir, Prithvi.
This isn't a dump-yard.
These are my experiments.
This is Principal Joshi.
I told you about him earlier.
[Device Beeping]
You know, there's something common
between machines and people.
They both don't realize when their
brains malfunction.
But machines don't have brains.
Some people don't have brains either.
I'll leave you guys to it.
Riaz will be waiting for me.
Bye!
Nilofer gave me your medical file.
We have a lot in common, Prithvi.
15 years ago, I lost my wife and
sons in a car accident.
I was depressed.
I attempted suicide multiple times.
But I survived.
Obviously!
Regression therapy, black magic,
I tried everything...
that could help people
like you and me.
To help us move on.
I have moved on.
Yeah?
It's wonderful.
You still see them right?
Sir, I don't want to disturb you.
Please carry on,
I'm also going to leave.
There are a few things I didn't
understand in your file...
like these drawings.
What are these drawings?
Side effects.
Of what?
You know what I mean, Sir.
I have not moved on.
When I don't take my
pills, I see Sapna and Megha.
I purposely avoid taking them, so
that I can see my family again.
So I don't lose them again.
That's when I see this
unrecognizable shadow.
My imaginary...
Ghost?
Hallucination
This imaginary ghost...
It could be real?
A spirit?
A bad omen?
Sir I have some extra
pills, I'll send them across.
Maybe you need them. Good night!
Tell me something, why does your
girlfriend keep calling me every day?
Well, if we keep fighting every day,
who else will she call?
But why every hour man?
Relax...
This beach can never stay clean.
It's become a junkyard.
The girl's body was found on
Juhu beach this morning.
According to our sources, the couple were last
seen on Juhu Beach, heading towards Sea Bird.
The Directorate General of
Shipping Agnihotri has said that
they are trying to move
Sea Bird from Juhu beach
but it doesn't look
like these efforts...
What the hell is happening?
Now Sea Bird will be blamed,
even if a fish dies in the ocean?
What's the status?
Sir, it's impossible for
our salvers to tow the ship.
I've spoken to the owner and told
him to hire a private salver.
I have doubled the fine too!
Diesel, sludge, toxic material?
Sir, there's no toxic material
but a lot of diesel on the ship.
If the diesel leaks,
the environmentalists will crucify us.
- When are you meeting the owner?
- Tomorrow.
Meet him today.
And get rid of that
ship from Juhu beach
now... understand!
- Right Sir.
- Go.
What are you saying?
There's nothing on the ship,
you've checked it right?
there's nothing there,
absolutely nothing.
Don't stress, I'm hiring the best
salvage company...
The engine room is shut.
Why?
What's in there?
Engine room?
There's nothing in there.
I swear,
there's nothing in the engine room.
I don't know if you'll believe
what I'm about to tell you.
What does that mean?
I've told him before.
Sea Bird is haunted!
Hey, this spiel won't save you.
Sir, Sea Bird has
a lot of mysterious stories,
with several disappearances
and deaths on board.
This one time, the ship was stuck at a
port due to a smuggling investigation.
The port workers were saying the
investigation was taking time
because it's a smuggling matter.
but the simple truth was that no
one wanted to board the ship.
They eventually fabricated the
report and released the ship.
But in February 2001,
Sea Bird's entire crew
disappeared overnight...how?
And do you think...
Sea Bird's tow rope
broke for the first time?
Jolly, give up smuggling
and become a writer.
Such a fascinating story. Wow!
I told you Sir,
you wouldn't believe me.
[Indistinct Chatter]
This is looking like
a tough task for our salvers.
Go get the report. Thanks.
Oh Almighty, if this ship moves today
I'll do some free charity.
What? That's all I can afford with
my salary.
Oh look, there's some movement.
Oh Shit!
We're screwed.
Hey, hey!
Prithvi... Prithvi...
Raju, Aslam. Prithvi... Go quickly!
Go quickly... Prithvi!
How long will it take?
Get me a boat.
What's got into in your head?
Why the hell did you go in the water?
- There were lifeguards on duty.
- Don't get started now
He's gone crazy and
he's driving me crazy too.
How are those two doing?
Who?
The worker and that girl.
Which girl?
Other than the worker,
there was a girl near the ship.
There was no girl there.
No...there was a girl.
I saw her.
Are you imagining things again?
Are you hallucinating?
Oh ok!
You saw something like this on the ship also?
That's why you took me along.
I'm going to make an appointment
with the doctor tomorrow.
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
There isn't one for kids.
There's no life jacket for kids,
Prithvi.
We'll wait here... you go!
Dad's found a solution.
Nothing's going to happen.
I promise!
Meghu.
That was a nice surprise trip,
Prithvi.
I told you that the life jacket was loose.
I could've stayed back with Megha.
But you didn't listen...
You promised us that nothing's
going to happen.
Answer me.
Dad
You made a tight knot, right?
How did it come undone?
I miss you a lot.
I want to come back to you.
I want to come back.
- I want to come back.
- I want to come back to you.
Riaz, answer the phone.
Pick up, Riaz.
Who's there?
Hello?
Wait!
Don't worry, I'm here to help you.
Hey!
Hello!
[Snapping]
Who's there?
[Knock on Door]
Prithvi?
[Door Bell]
[Snapping]
I need to board that ship urgently.
Sir there's a high tide,
it will be tough.
Arrange a boat, quickly.
My friend is stuck on the ship, go!
Help!
[Snapping]
I'm going to request Agnihotri to
get us off this Sea Bird case.
Meera, are you playing with toys?
Look there, say Hi Dad.
Say it aloud, Hi
Look who's here.
- Hi Mummy, Hi!
- Hi Mummy!
1...2...3
Meera!
This video is from Meera's
3rd birthday.
Remember, Patel said that the ship
was haunted?
Yes
The hauntings have been mentioned
in these logbooks.
Look...
Here.
A young girl was spotted on this ship.
Her age, approximately, 7-8 years.
8 years.
That girl we saw yesterday,
how old could she be?
Vaguely? Around 13-14 years old?
I don't understand
what your trying to say.
Meera, the girl in the video...
she's the same girl who is mentioned
in these logbooks,
and the same girl we
saw on the ship yesterday.
Meera is alive!
Are you crazy?
I've seen her.
She didn't look anything like a
living person, Prithvi.
I don't know about that, but I do
know that the dead don't grow older.
So an evil spirit?
What rubbish?
It's not rubbish Riaz.
If what Prithvi is saying is right,
if that girl is really alive,
that means she is possessed.
Possessed!
We must help her then.
Why? Why do you want to help her?
Because nobody else will.
We can't help her...
until we know what has
possessed her and why.
We need to find out
about this evil spirit
or we won't be able to help her.
Sunder
Listen, I want Sea Bird's
entire records
for every time the ship arrived
and departed Indian shores.
I want the full crew
list, year wise.
No, 2 days will get too late.
Hmm...
Sunder, please try to get it by
tomorrow.
Yeah please, thank you.
Riaz?
- Yeah
- I need a favor.
Tell me.
Smuggling was thriving in the 90's.
See if Sea Bird's
name pops up anywhere?
Start with this port.
Why do you have to
pry into everything?
Why don't you hand over
that video to the police?
And what will we tell them?
There's a girl on that ship,
who's been possessed.
Find her and bring her
out so that we can exorcise her?
Your forgetting, the Police couldn't
even find that missing boy's body.
Riaz.
What's happened to you?
Look, I understand you want to
help that girl.
I also do. But how do
we know if she's even alive?
I've seen her.
Living people don't look like that.
Evil spirits, ghosts, possession...
this is not our job Prithvi.
And what if you relapse?
Don't worry about me Riaz,
I'll be fine.
There's no guarantee that she's alive
but if there's a slight
chance that she is...
and she is Meera,
I will get her out of the ship,
no matter what.
And you think doing this will
bring your daughter back?
Prithvi.
[Knock On Door]
Papa, Papa.
Meghu.
Papa.
Meghu, Papa.
Come to me.
Meghu, I'm coming.
Please come to me.
I'm coming.
It's not real, It's not real...
Yeah, I got the files.
Thank you.
Listen, are these all
the records or are there more?
Was there any woman on the crew?
Please try again?
Thank you.
[Phone Dialing]
Hello
He passed away few years ago.
I have no idea.
I'm sorry, he's no more.
He expired 10 year back.
Hello
He died on the ship.
[Snapping]
[Knock On Door]
Coming!
Give me a second.
[Knock On Door]
[Door Bell]
Prithvi...
Meera's mother recorded this
man in the tapes, time and again.
Why?
No idea, sir
Did you find out anything
about Meera's family?
He has some unfinished business,
that's why he's kept
Meera alive for so long.
Sir, we don't have time
to solve this puzzle.
Sea Bird will be towed soon.
We have to find a way to help her.
There are many ways Prithvi...
but we don't know for how long this child
has been possessed by the evil spirit.
Meera could get killed
if we try to exorcise her.
It has to let her go by itself.
Prithvi, this spirit could've
killed you the day it saw you
but it purposely kept you alive.
It wants to use you as a medium.
It's no coincidence
that you keep seeing Meera.
Sorry for the other day.
I'll always be by your side,
no matter how crazy you are.
I contacted Oman port,
and found records about Sea Bird.
The crew that committed
suicide in 2001,
is the same crew that was on Sea Bird,
in 1998.
Sea Bird was caught
at Oman Port in 1998,
for some illegal activities.
The crew was released
due to diplomatic ties
but the ship was
stuck there for 3 years.
Crew list?
Here.
There's only one name that's
different from the 2001 crew list.
Vandana.
Any other information?
There's nothing in the records
but some emails were
sent from Oman
in which...
this photo was found.
This church is on the
outskirts of the city.
Excuse me! How may I help you?
We're here from the shipping office.
Do you know her?
[Indistinct Chatter]
We found her belongings on a ship so we
just wanted some information about her.
Do you know of any acquaintance
that can help us?
Why do you need any acquaintance?
Vandana ma'am is right inside.
[Lullaby]
Meera, are you playing with toys?
Look at what Dad brought us--
Camera!
You know,
we have to record videos and show Dad,
how much food Meera's eaten
and how strong she's become.
Oh Meera, you've become so big.
You sit here,
keep the doll next to you,
and the three of us
will eat our food together.
You like it?
Look there. Look at the
camera, say Hi Dad.
Hi!
Meera...
My name is Prithvi, I'm the
surveying officer on Sea Bird.
This is Professor Joshi.
Meera, Vandana...
Meera is alive!
Your daughter is alive...
and has been on Sea
Bird for the past 11 years.
We have very little time.
Sea Bird will be towed any time
now, taking Meera with it forever.
We just need your help.
Who is he?
What happened?
Who's this?
He...
This is Megha.
I know how it feels
to lose a daughter.
I can't bring her back.
You're getting a chance Vandana...
save Meera.
Is Meera really alive?
Vandana, what happened on Sea Bird?
Sea Bird...
A lot of illegal things
happened on board.
The whole crew was involved.
The Captain created a
secret room on the ship
for smuggling.
It was impossible to find this room.
Drugs, gold, antiques...
there was nothing that
Sea Bird didn't smuggle.
Anyone who tried to speak up was...
I had only one dream...
to have a happy family,
but Captain was an alcoholic,
and would regularly beat me.
I couldn't handle it anymore.
I decided to commit suicide.
Amar,
an ordinary Seaman
fell in love with me.
Amar...
Captain would beat me
and Amar would comfort me.
We got very close in no time.
We decided to run away.
We made a plan to expose Captain and
started recording the contraband secretly.
The ship was due to arrive
in India in a few weeks.
We had collected enough evidence.
But Amar continued recording
and someone saw him with the camera.
When Captain found out about this,
he ordered for Amar to be killed.
But he couldn't kill him because Amar
hid those tapes somewhere.
Captain was forced to keep Amar alive
till he disclosed where the tapes were.
Amar was tortured a lot
but he did not reveal anything
about the tapes.
2 days later, he was dead.
Why where you still with Captain
after all this?
Because I got pregnant.
Captain was very happy.
He stopped beating me.
But he had no idea
that Meera wasn't his
but Amar's child.
That's why he's kept Meera with him.
[Phone Ringing]
Riaz, I'll call you
back in sometime.
[Speaking Indistinctly]
Yeah, we're leaving now.
The tug boat's been attached.
They'll move Sea Bird tomorrow,
we only have tonight.
Secret Room!
Meera's in the secret room...
and only I can take you there.
You wait here.
Why?
You're the last surviving
member of the crew.
It's not safe for you to enter.
What about the Secret Room?
Riaz?
Use this to help us get there
and leave right after that.
Prithvi.
[Device Beeping]
Riaz, over there.
Take this.
Prithvi.
- Prithvi.
- Prithvi, Prithvi.
Prithvi.
[Device Beeping]
Prithvi, Prithvi.
Are you okay?
Prithvi.
Riaz.
Shit!
C'mon.
Riaz.
Prithvi, let's go.
Vandana?
Yes, Prithvi?
Vandana, where do we
go from the engine room?
Prithvi, can you hear me?
Engine room?
Where do we go from here?
Go down, enter the oil filter room.
- Vandana
- Yes...Yes Prithvi
Vandana.
Prithvi,
where are you, I can't hear you.
Vandana, Vandana.
Vandana, hello Vandana
Meera?
Meera!
[Giggling]
[Chanting]
[Device Beeping]
He's somewhere close.
Then the secret room
must be close by too.
[Device Beeping]
Prithvi, Prithvi?
What are you doing Prithvi?
Let's leave from here.
Vandana, Hello Vandana...
Hello Vandana...
Vandana!
Prithvi.
Where is the diesel leaking from...
Top Deck?
Diesel!
We need to find the body.
Sir...
[Chanting]
[Lullaby]
Vandana
Vandana,
we warned you not to come down here.
I won't leave without Meera.
You need to leave right now.
Amar...
I'm pregnant with your child.
I love you Amar.
I love you.
You killed Amar?
If Captain would've found
out about us,
he would've killed me as well.
And I couldn't let Meera die.
Meera.
- Vandana.
- Meera.
Vandana, Vandana.
Amar!
Please forgive me.
It was my fault.
Let Meera go.
I know you want to
keep her with you
but she's my child too.
This is no place for Meera.
Please let me see her once,
then you can kill me.
[Chanting]